# Aya Nae'l AL\_Awesat

#### Computer Engineering

Developer specializing in front-end development, familiar with several programming languages including HTML, Java, JS, C++, C and CSS. Moreover, knowledge in back-end of the ASP.Net Framework language. Also, strong background on projects management and customer relations. In addition, to software projects, I have knowledge of hardware projects and the method of analyzing any project in all respects in order to design it on the ground.

<u>aawesat2000@gmail.com</u>

+972 512532477

11 01 February 2000

GPA: 86.6%

https://github.com/aya https://www.linkedin.com

### **EDUCATION**

### **Android Development Track** Online

2021 - 2022. GPA: 97.66%

"1 MILLION JORDANIAN CODERS INITIATIVE"

 I passed an intensive course in the field Android Development Track offered by Udacity over 6 consecutive months.

### **Bachelor Of In Computer Engineering**

Al-Quds University, Abu Dis, Palestine

2019 - 2023. GPA: 86.84%

Software & Hardware Courses

 I recently graduated after four and a half years... I took many courses in the field of software and hardware (Network, Embedded, OS... etc,). Also, implemented many projects(HW & SW).

#### **Tawjehe Degree**

Scientific Branch

2017 - 2018.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Smart Parking**

Palestine Science and Technology Exhibition 2016 - 2017.

#### Alarm & Surveillance System

**Experts Turnkey Solutions** 

2021 - 11/2022.

### Oddo Program

Jaffa.Net.Software

2021 - 11/2022.

#### ASP.Net Framework

Programmers For Technology & Software Services Co. **LANGUAGES** 10/2023 - 12/2023.

### **SKILLS**

Strong Decision Maker Complex Problem Solver Creative Design Service-Focused **Time Management** 

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Software Project (Legal4u) (04/2022 - 06/2022)

 The main purpose of this software project is to provide a user-friendly environment for lawyers and aims to increase the efficiency and productivity of lawyers, making it user-friendly for clients as well. The website provides facilities like online registration and create profile.

Hardware Project (Smart Bathroom) (03/2021 -05/2021)

 The bathroom is an integral part of people's everyday life, there is now a whole host of gadgets that can help bring your bathroom into the future, the evolution of ordinary bathrooms into sophisticated smart bathrooms made human life easier, faster, more comfortable also economical. The bathroom includes a smart faucet, soap, toilet, shower, and bathtub and lights... etc.

Hardware Project (Control System Of Home Automation By Using SHOOW Application) (10/2022 - 01/2023)

This home automation project is powered by a Raspberry Pi. An automated home is a system that uses a mobile app to control basic home features and operations automatically over the SHOOW network. It aims to use less electricity and offer better security services.

## CERTIFICATES

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1wuNKLFIYh79pJoJ rP2YYnRh8oSBc2Hx8?usp=share link

Arabic Native or Bilingual Proficiency English Writing: Excellent Conversation: Good